AARON WHITE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER ATLANTA, GA 404.985.1476 | AARONAWHITE1@GMAIL.COM

ONLINE PRESENCE

PORTFOLIO

AARONAWHITE.COM

GITHUB

GITHUB.COM/ AARONIOUSBLANCO

LINKEDIN

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/
AARON-ALEXANDER-WHITE/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT	EXPRESS
REACT	POSGRESQL
REDUX	JQUERY
PYTHON	CSS3
NODE.IS	HTML5

TECHNICAL EDUCATION

DIGITALCRAFTS

16 WEEK FULL-TIME
IMMERSIVE WEB
DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM
FEB. 2017 - PRESENT

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA

BA INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS
HISTORY MINOR
(MAGNA CUM LAUDE)
2008

WAKE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE
CERTIFICATE
2015



PROFILE

A quick study with a particularly adaptable skillset and a comprehensive track record of exceeding ambitious goals in the political and non-profit sectors.

Experienced in data collection, reporting, and analysis; staff recruitment, development, and management; partner engagement, convening, and training; and project design and execution.



FEATURED WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

GetFresh - A web app for farmers market shoppers.

Live site: getfreshapp.us

- Centerpiece of the application is a zip code search feature that makes three separate API calls (using the USDA API and Google Maps API)
- Includes a recipe search feature allowing users to search by ingredients purchased at their local market (utilizes the Yummly API)
- Additional features include account creation/authentication and market reviews (by logged in users)
- Built with JavaScript, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, CSS, and HTML.

Yahtzee - The Dice Game

Live site: yahtzee.aaronawhite.com

- A web app designed to resemble the 90s-style, handheld version of the famous game
- Built with React.js, CSS, and HTML.

Tic-Tac-Toe - The Classic Game

Live site: tic-tac-toe-game.aaronawhite.com

- Features single and two player options.
- Built with JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, and HTML

ONLINE PRESENCE

PORTFOLIO

AARONAWHITE.COM

GITHUB

GITHUB.COM/
AARONIOUSBLANCO

LINKEDIN

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/
AARON-ALEXANDER-WHITE/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT EXPRESS
REACT POSGRESQL
REDUX JQUERY
PYTHON CSS3
NODE.JS HTML5

TECHNICAL EDUCATION

DIGITAL CRAFTS

16 WEEK FULL-TIME
IMMERSIVE WEB
DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM
FEB. 2017 - PRESENT

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF GEORGIA

BA INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS
HISTORY MINOR
(MAGNA CUM LAUDE)
2008

WAKE TECHNICAL COMMUNITY COLLEGE

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE
CERTIFICATE
2015

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- DEPUTY STATE DIRECTOR | ENROLL AMERICA NC
- Oversaw the statewide consumer and partner engagement program in North Carolina
- Managed a statewide team of 5 Deputy Regional Directors in addition to 2 Special Project Organizers in SC
- Played a primary role in state plan design and execution
- Consistently in the top three performing EA staffed states
- Oversaw two hospital contract special projects—one in NC and one in SC—including the recruitment and management of project staff, the implementation of the patient engagement program, hospital staff training, and regular reporting to hospital leadership.
- Served as the press contact for Enroll America at local events, providing interviews to television, radio, and print outlets.

REGIONAL ORGANIZING LEAD | ENROLL AMERICA - NC Raleigh, NC • 2013 to 2015

BUNCOMBE COUNTY FIELD ORGANIZER | ORGANIZING FOR AMERICA - NC

Asheville, NC • 2012

LAUNCH DIRECTOR | CALIFORNIA DEMOCRATIC PARTY CANVASS OFFICE Oakland, CA • 2011 to 2012

DEPUTY FIELD DIRECTOR | CATHERINE PUGH FOR MAYORBaltimore, MD • 2011

LEGISLATIVE AIDE | GEORGIA STATE REPRESENTATIVES SCOTT HOLCOMB AND RASHAD TAYLOR

Atlanta, GA • 2011

COORDINATED CAMPAIGN FIELD DIRECTOR | DEMOCRATIC PARTY OF GEORGIA

Atlanta, GA • 2010

ENGLISH LANGUAGE TEACHER | UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

Iquique, Chile • 2009